[Being A Hero]
[كونك بطل]
[Episode 15]
[الحلقة 15]
I need to use the toilet.
أنا بحاجة لاستخدام المرحاض.
You can head there first.
يمكنك التوجه إلى هناك أولاً.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Examine
فحص
the truck again.
الشاحنة مرة أخرى.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Do not omit
لا تحذف
the licenses,
التراخيص ،
custom clearance documents,
وثائق التخليص الجمركي ،
and the list of goods.
وقائمة البضائع.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Beware of Jiang Lei when you receive the goods
احذر من Jiang Lei عند استلام البضائع
in the tea factory.
في مصنع الشاي.
You need to examine them thoroughly.
تحتاج إلى فحصها بدقة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
This isn't my first time
هذه ليست المرة الأولى لي
taking the same path.
يسلك نفس المسار.
If so, I'll head to the airport now.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك ، سأتوجه إلى المطار الآن.
[Wanlutong Logistics]
[Wanlutong اللوجستية]
Mr. Yu.
السيد يو.
Must we do so?
هل يجب أن نفعل ذلك؟
Understood.
مفهوم.
Relax.
الاسترخاء.
We'll depart in just a moment.
سنغادر خلال لحظة.
Director Lin,
المخرج لين ،
Group One is in position.
المجموعة الأولى في المركز.
Group Two is in position.
المجموعة الثانية في الموقف.
Group Four is in position.
المجموعة الرابعة في المركز.
Sir,
سيد،
Group Five is in position.
المجموعة الخامسة في المركز.
Sir, Group Six is in position.
سيدي ، المجموعة السادسة في موقعها.
Roger that.
استلمت هذا.
All groups, execute the initial plan.
جميع المجموعات ، تنفيذ الخطة الأولية.
Someone's here!
شخص ما هنا!
Sir, the target has appeared.
سيدي ، الهدف قد ظهر.
[Public Security Bureau Monitoring System] Group One, stay alert.
[نظام مراقبة مكتب الأمن العام] المجموعة الأولى ، ابق في حالة تأهب.
They're heading toward your side.
إنهم يتجهون نحو جانبك.
Roger that.
استلمت هذا.
Sir,
سيد،
the target has entered the tea factory.
دخل الهدف مصنع الشاي.
All groups, keep an eye on them.
كل المجموعات ، راقبهم.
Do not give away your positions.
لا تتنازل عن مواقفك.
Sir,
سيد،
the members of the factory have met up with them.
التقى بهم أعضاء المصنع.
The target is heading toward the packaging workshop.
الهدف يتجه نحو ورشة التعبئة والتغليف.
Everyone, take note.
الجميع ، لاحظوا.
Do not
لاتفعل
omit any details or corners.
حذف أي تفاصيل أو زوايا.
We must procure complete evidence.
يجب علينا الحصول على أدلة كاملة.
-Got it.
-فهمتك.  -فهمتك.
All right, leave.
حسنًا ، اترك.
Gou,
قو ،
Dong said
قال دونغ
you guys must
يا رفاق يجب
do Guishou and Wu Zhenfeng in
هل Guishou و Wu Zhenfeng in
before the cops are here.
قبل رجال الشرطة هنا.
Don't you understand me?
الا تفهمني
We have to do Guishou
علينا أن نفعل Guishou
and Wu Zhenfeng in.
ووو Zhenfeng في.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Why are you still standing there?
لماذا لا تزال واقفا هناك؟
Get to work!
اذهب للعمل!
[Smuggling is prohibited]
[التهريب محظور]
Director Lin,
المخرج لين ،
Group Three is in position.
المجموعة الثالثة في المركز.
did my phone
فعل هاتفي
receive any text messages?
تلقي أي رسائل نصية؟
Chen Yu, do not be distracted.
تشين يو ، لا تشتت انتباهك.
You're on a mission.
أنت في مهمة.
But Director Lin...
لكن المخرج لين ...
There are no buts!
لا يوجد لكن!
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
What's wrong with you today?
ما هو الخطأ معك اليوم؟
Who do you think
من تظن
it will be?
سيكون ذلك؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Do you think
هل تعتقد
we might encounter
قد نواجه
someone we know today?
شخص نعرفه اليوم؟
Are you referring to Wu Zhenfeng?
هل تشير إلى وو تشن فنغ؟
He...
هو...
He didn't come back last night.
لم يعد الليلة الماضية.
He said he was
قال إنه كان
heading to Walin Town tonight
متوجهًا إلى مدينة والين الليلة
to investigate his dad's case.
للتحقيق في قضية والده.
Did you see him today?
هل رأيته اليوم؟
What did you tell him?
بماذا أخبرته؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
This conversation never took place.
هذه المحادثة لم تحدث قط.
Chen Yu,
تشين يو ،
what if he was truly behind this deal,
ماذا لو كان حقاً وراء هذه الصفقة ،
and he didn't come
ولم يأت
because you tipped him off?
لأنك أعطيته معلومات؟
This is so important!
هذا مهم جدا!
Why didn't you report it to our superiors?
لماذا لم تبلغ رؤسائنا بذلك؟
How do I report it to them?
كيف أبلغهم بذلك؟
Tell me, how can I do it?
قل لي كيف أفعل ذلك؟
I said nothing.
قلت: لا شيء.
He told me to trust him.
قال لي أن أثق به.
He promised me
لقد وعدني
that he would tell me if he has any news.
أنه سيخبرني إذا كان لديه أي أخبار.
He told you to trust him?
قال لك أن تثق به؟
If he's here,
إذا كان هنا ،
you'll be fine.
ستكون بخير.
But if he's not here
لكن إذا لم يكن هنا
or something happens
أو شيء ما يحدث
to the deal tonight,
لصفقة الليلة ،
how do you plan to explain yourself?
كيف تخطط لشرح نفسك؟
Fine, even though you didn't tell him,
بخير ، رغم أنك لم تخبره ،
could you be sure
هل يمكن ان تكون متأكدا
that he didn't feel this at all?
أنه لم يشعر بهذا على الإطلاق؟
Did you think he had no idea about this?
هل تعتقد أنه ليس لديه فكرة عن هذا؟
If he did so
إذا فعل ذلك
for revenge,
للإنتقام،
he would surely tell me about it.
من المؤكد أنه سيخبرني عنها.
Just like what he did with Shu's case.
تمامًا مثل ما فعله بقضية شو.
In my opinion,
فى رايى،
we've spent a lot of time together.
قضينا الكثير من الوقت معًا.
He should trust me.
يجب أن يثق بي.
He should?
يجب عليه؟
He should trust you?
يجب أن يثق بك؟
Has it ever occurred to you
هل حدث لك ذلك من قبل
that he might not
أنه قد لا يفعل
just be back for revenge?
فقط سأعود من أجل الانتقام؟
What if he deceived you
ماذا لو خدعك
and manipulated you?
وتلاعب بك؟
Chen Yu,
تشين يو ،
he's a drug dealer.
إنه تاجر مخدرات.
[China]
[الصين]
This is your first time smuggling drugs.
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي تقوم فيها بتهريب المخدرات.
You must ensure your safety.
يجب عليك التأكد من سلامتك.
If you're in danger,
إذا كنت في خطر ،
you can abandon the goods.
يمكنك التخلي عن البضائع.
Prioritize your safety.
إعطاء الأولوية لسلامتك.
I understand.
أفهم.
All of us will be done for
كل واحد منا سوف ينتهي من أجله
if you get arrested.
إذا تم القبض عليك.
I hope you have a smooth journey.
أتمنى لك رحلة سلسة.
I've already prayed to the heavens.
لقد صليت بالفعل الى السماء.
You will be blessed.
سوف تبارك.
I will be extra careful.
سأكون أكثر حذرا.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Here, Feng.
هنا ، فنغ.
Chief Liu,
رئيس ليو ،
the goods have entered the border.
دخلت البضائع الحدود.
There's around 40 to 50 kg here.
يوجد حوالي 40 إلى 50 كجم هنا.
The drug smuggler
مهرب مخدرات
is Wu Zhenfeng.
هو وو Zhenfeng.
Did you catch the number plate?
هل التقطت لوحة الأرقام؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
I only know that one of them is a black
أنا أعرف فقط أن أحدهم أسود
Beijing-Hyundai SUV.
بكين-هيونداي SUV.
Do not alert them to our presence.
لا تنبههم لوجودنا.
Try your best to procure more evidence.
ابذل قصارى جهدك للحصول على المزيد من الأدلة.
Roger that.
استلمت هذا.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Time to go.
وقت الذهاب.
Director Lin,
المخرج لين ،
we've tracked down the black
لقد تعقبنا الأسود
Beijing-Hyundai SUV.
بكين-هيونداي SUV.
Its number plate is
لوحة رقمها
Cang F96920.
تسانغ F96920.
It's a fake number plate.
إنها لوحة أرقام مزيفة.
It's heading toward the tea factory.
إنه يتجه نحو مصنع الشاي.
Group One, take note.
المجموعة الأولى ، لاحظ.
The vehicles will enter the tea factory soon.
ستدخل السيارات مصنع الشاي قريبًا.
Get ready.
إستعد.
Roger that.
استلمت هذا.
Yang Yi, Chen Yu,
يانغ يي ، تشن يو ،
join Group One.
الانضمام إلى المجموعة الأولى.
Be on standby.
كن على أهبة الاستعداد.
-Roger that.
-استلمت هذا.  -استلمت هذا.
(Did you really head there)
(هل توجهت حقًا إلى هناك)
(just to buy medicine?)
(فقط لشراء الدواء؟)
[Yunhui Pharmacy] (Why did you think I was there then?)
[صيدلية يونهوي] (لماذا كنت تعتقد أنني كنت هناك حينها؟)
(Have you ever seen a drug dealer)
(هل رأيت تاجر مخدرات من قبل)
(turn himself in before?)
(تسليم نفسه من قبل؟)
(Last night,)
(ليلة أمس،)
(I went to Walin Town.)
(ذهبت إلى مدينة والين).
(I endured for the past three years)
(لقد تحملت في السنوات الثلاث الماضية)
(so that I could avenge my dad.)
(حتى أتمكن من الانتقام من والدي.)
You must trust me.
يجب أن تثق بي.
Trust me.
صدقني.
Chen Yu.
تشن يو.
Chen Yu?
تشن يو؟
Don't be distracted.
لا تشتت انتباهك.
We're on a mission.
نحن في مهمة.
Gou.
جو.
What's with the heavy diesel smell?
ما برائحة الديزل الثقيل؟
I know, right?
أنا أوافق؟
The machinery here is old.
الآلات هنا قديمة.
They operate on diesel.
تعمل على الديزل.
Examine the goods.
افحص البضائع.
Chief Liu.
رئيس ليو.
Gou,
قو ،
this isn't it.
هذا ليس هو.
This is lime powder.
هذا مسحوق الجير.
Are you sure?
هل أنت واثق؟
Yes.
نعم.
Director Lin,
المخرج لين ،
they're examining the goods.
إنهم يفحصون البضائع.
Something
شئ ما
seems off.
يبدو خارج.
I think
أظن
that the deal might go south.
أن الصفقة قد تذهب جنوبًا.
What?
ماذا؟
Lime powder?
مسحوق الجير؟
What do you mean by this?
ما الذي تعنيه بهذا؟
Did you think all of my men
هل فكرت في كل رجالي
came here to play with you all?
جئت هنا للعب معكم جميعا؟
Gou,
قو ،
I was there
كنت هناك
when they repackaged the goods.
عندما أعادوا تغليف البضائع.
This is impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm going to make a call.
سأقوم بإجراء مكالمة.
Shut the door!
اغلق الباب!
None of you
لا احد منكم
will leave this place alive!
سيترك هذا المكان حيا!
Beat them up!
اهزمهم!
Don't do it!
لا تفعل ذلك!
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
We can't see what's going on at all.
لا يمكننا رؤية ما يحدث على الإطلاق.
Dong,
دونغ ،
the goods are fake.
البضائع مزيفة.
What?
ماذا؟
Dong, Mengka delivered lime powder to us.
Dong، Mengka سلمتنا مسحوق الجير إلينا.
The goods are fake.
البضائع مزيفة.
Dong,
دونغ ،
do we burn it down?
هل نحرقه؟
Is Wu Zhenfeng around?
هل وو Zhenfeng موجود؟
Yes.
نعم.
Burn it down.
إحرقه تمامآ.
Chief Liu, the factory is on fire!
الرئيس ليو ، المصنع مشتعل!
Let's go!
لنذهب!
Director Lin,
المخرج لين ،
they're fighting right now.
إنهم يقاتلون الآن.
The tea factory is on fire.
مصنع الشاي يحترق.
Please give us your order.
يرجى اعطاءنا طلبك.
Speak.
يتكلم.
Deputy Chief Chen,
نائب الرئيس تشين ،
the tea factory
مصنع الشاي
is on fire.
انه يحترق.
And they are fighting each other.
وهم يقاتلون بعضهم البعض.
What?
ماذا؟
Retreat!
تراجع!
Hurry!
عجل!
One, two, three!
واحد اثنين ثلاثة!
Deputy Chief Chen,
نائب الرئيس تشين ،
the fire is spreading
الحريق ينتشر
at a rapid rate.
بمعدل سريع.
Please give us your order!
يرجى اعطاءنا طلبك!
Charge inside!
شحن في الداخل!
Do not let them escape!
لا تدعهم يهربون!
Yes, sir!
نعم سيدي!
Remember,
تذكر،
the safety of our men
سلامة رجالنا
is our priority.
هي أولويتنا.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
All groups, take note.
جميع المجموعات ، لاحظ.
Move out.
تحرك للخارج.
Do not let any suspects
لا تدع أي مشتبه بهم
escape the scene.
الهروب من المشهد.
Everyone, listen up.
الجميع ، استمع.
Charge into the tea factory!
اشحن إلى مصنع الشاي!
Roger that.
استلمت هذا.
Move out!
تحرك للخارج!
Get up!
استيقظ!
Feng!
فنغ!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
The factory is crumbling!
المصنع ينهار!
Feng!
فنغ!
Run!
يجري!
Just run!
فقط اركض!
Feng!
فنغ!
Freeze!
تجمد!
The cops are here!
رجال الشرطة هنا!
Run!
يجري!
Don't move!
لا تتحرك!
Stop running!
توقف عن الركض!
Stop right there!
توقف هناك!
Don't move!
لا تتحرك!
Hurry! Put out the fire!
عجل!  اخماد الحريق!
Hurry!
عجل!
Put out the fire!
اخماد الحريق!
Don't move!
لا تتحرك!
Wu Zhenfeng, freeze!
وو Zhenfeng ، تجمد!
Step back!
خطوة للخلف!
Put out the fire!
اخماد الحريق!
-Over here! -Hurry!
-هنا!  -عجل!
Is anyone hurt?
هل تضرر أحد؟
Hurry! Over here!
عجل!  هنا!
Put out the fire!
اخماد الحريق!
Take him away!
يأخذه بعيدا!
My factory!
مصنعي!
Save it!
احفظها!
Stop the car.
أوقف السيارة.
Let's go!
لنذهب!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Hello, Mr. Wan.
مرحبا سيد وان.
We're in huge trouble.
نحن في ورطة كبيرة.
The tea factory caught on fire,
اشتعلت النيران في مصنع الشاي ،
and cops have already surrounded the area.
وقد حاصر رجال الشرطة المنطقة بالفعل.
Kun,
متي،
the cops have been lured away.
تم إغراء رجال الشرطة بعيدًا.
Send out the goods.
أرسل البضائع.
Got it.
فهمتك.
Let's go!
لنذهب!
Be careful!
كن حذرا!
Get us more fire extinguishers!
تجلب لنا المزيد من طفايات الحريق!
Okay!
تمام!
Hurry!
عجل!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
[Weishi Ark] [Shengjiang]
[سفينة ويشي] [شنغجيانغ]
Dong,
دونغ ،
the goods have arrived safely.
وصلت البضائع بأمان.
I saw Mr. Wan.
رأيت السيد وان.
Mr. Wan.
السيد وان.
You've waited for the entire night.
لقد انتظرت طوال الليل.
It must've been tough.
يجب أن يكون الأمر صعبًا.
Hao Dong,
هاو دونغ ،
what do you mean by this?
ما الذي تعنيه بهذا؟
Were you planning
هل كنت تخطط
to just brush it off
لمجرد التخلص منه
if I didn't call you?
اذا لم اتصل بك
Who do you take me for?
لمن تأخذني؟
Let me ask you this!
دعني أسألك هذا!
Why didn't you tell me
لماذا لم تخبرني
about your plan?
حول خطتك؟
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Mr. Wan,
السيد وان ،
you wouldn't have been as convincing with your act
لم تكن مقنعًا بعملك
if I had told you earlier.
إذا كنت قد أخبرتك في وقت سابق.
Do you know
هل تعرف
that you're digging your own grave here?
أنك تحفر قبرك هنا؟
We've messed up the deal with Mengka!
لقد أفسدنا الصفقة مع Mengka!
Do you think they'll let us off?
هل تعتقد أنهم سوف يتركوننا؟
Name?
اسم؟
Liu Dazhuang.
ليو داتشوانغ.
Gender?
جنس؟
Male.
ذكر.
Where did you come from?
من أين أتيت؟
I'm not a local.
أنا لست من السكان المحليين.
I came here to make a living.
جئت إلى هنا لكسب لقمة العيش.
How long have you been here?
منذ متى وأنت هنا؟
Around six months.
حوالي ستة أشهر.
All right.
حسنا.
What about you?
وماذا عنك؟
We came from the same place.
لقد جئنا من نفس المكان.
I came here to make a living too.
جئت إلى هنا لكسب لقمة العيش أيضا.
Dad!
أب!
Someone!
شخصا ما!
Help!
مساعدة!
(This isn't it.)
(هذا ليس هو.)
(This is lime powder.)
(هذا مسحوق الجير.)
(Shut the door!)
(اغلق الباب!)
(None of you)
(لا احد منكم)
(shall leave this place alive!)
(يجب ترك هذا المكان حيا!)
(Beat them up!)
(اهزمهم!)
(Feng, run!)
(فنغ ، اركض!)
Wu Zhenfeng,
وو زهينفنغ ،
raise your head.
ارفع رأسك.
Who's this person
من هذا الشخص
who sent you to the border?
من ارسلك الى الحدود
Is he a member of Mengka?
هل هو عضو في Mengka؟
(You're Guishou?)
(أنت Guishou؟)
Do you know me?
هل تعرفني؟
(You must be a cop.)
(يجب أن تكون شرطيًا.)
Fine, it's my fault.
حسنا ، هذا خطأي.
(I'll follow your instruction.)
(سأتبع تعليماتك.)
Wu Zhenfeng,
وو زهينفنغ ،
where are the real drugs?
اين المخدرات الحقيقية؟
(Feng,)
(فنغ)
(why don't we head back?)
(لماذا لا نعود؟)
You may be able to return to Mengka
قد تتمكن من العودة إلى مينكا
without any issues.
بدون أي مشاكل.
But what about me?
ولكن ماذا عني؟
(I'm sure Dong)
(أنا متأكد من دونغ)
(is trying to kill us here.)
(يحاول قتلنا هنا).
(Dong is ruthless in Yunhe.)
(دونغ لا يرحم في Yunhe).
Wu Zhenfeng, listen up.
وو Zhenfeng ، استمع.
Don't think that you'll get away easily
لا تعتقد أنك ستهرب بسهولة
just because the drugs were fake.
فقط لأن الأدوية كانت مزيفة.
You're a drug dealer.
أنت تاجر مخدرات.
(Feng!)
(فنغ!)
The factory is crumbling!
المصنع ينهار!
Feng!
فنغ!
But judging from your expression,
لكن انطلاقا من تعبيرك ،
it seems like you were in the dark.
يبدو أنك كنت في الظلام.
Do you know
هل تعرف
who set you up?
من أقامك
Why did you head to the tea factory
لماذا توجهت إلى مصنع الشاي
that night?
تلك الليلة؟
To make some money.
لكسب بعض المال.
Who recruited you?
من جندك؟
Guishou.
Guishou.
Gou brought me there.
أحضرني غو هناك.
Who recruited you?
من جندك؟
Gou.
جو.
Tell me the time and location.
قل لي الوقت والمكان.
It was on the 14th.
كان يوم 14.
As for the location,
اما عن الموقع
it was in the alley of an urban village.
كان في زقاق قرية حضرية.
It was on the 14th,
كان يوم 14 ،
in an urban village.
في قرية حضرية.
It was on the 14th, in an urban village.
كان يوم 14 في قرية حضرية.
Who else was present?
من كان حاضرًا أيضًا؟
Ma.
أماه.
And Dou.
ودو.
And Lei...
و Lei ...
Lei.
لي.
The second screen.
الشاشة الثانية.
(How did you guys enter the tea factory?)
(كيف دخلتم مصنع الشاي؟)
(Gou brought me in.)
(أحضرني جو.)
(He knew the people there.)
(كان يعرف الناس هناك).
(Do you know)
(هل تعرف)
(the people who met up with you?)
(الناس الذين التقوا بك؟)
(I don't.)
(أنا لا.)
It was Gou's connection.
كان اتصال غو.
Gou again?
قو مرة أخرى؟
You beat up Gou Sheng in his house,
لقد ضربت غو شنغ في منزله ،
yet you still refer to him so politely?
ومع ذلك ما زلت تشير إليه بأدب شديد؟
I beat him up because he owed me some money.
ضربته لأنه مدين لي ببعض المال.
He paid up
دفع
and introduced this job to me.
وقدم لي هذه الوظيفة.
I have to listen to him.
لا بد لي من الاستماع إليه.
That's the rule.
هذه هي القاعدة.
These two are different matters.
هذان أمران مختلفان.
Gou
جو
and Guishou
و Guishou
are very close with Wu Zhenfeng.
قريبون جدًا من Wu Zhenfeng.
Officer,
ضابط،
Wu Zhenfeng was smuggling drugs.
كان Wu Zhenfeng يهرب المخدرات.
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
But I didn't do so.
لكنني لم أفعل ذلك.
I don't dare to do so.
لا أجرؤ على القيام بذلك.
You said Wu Zhenfeng was smuggling drugs.
قلت أن وو زهين فنغ كان يهرب المخدرات.
Do you have any proof?
هل لديك أي دليل؟
He comes from Mengka.
لقد جاء من Mengka.
In a place
في مكان
like Mengka,
مثل منكا
everyone is doing drugs.
الجميع يتعاطون المخدرات.
Seems like you know Wu Zhenfeng quite well.
يبدو أنك تعرف Wu Zhenfeng جيدًا.
How many times have you seen him?
كم مرة رأيته؟
I don't know him well.
لا أعرفه جيدًا.
Today's our first encounter.
اليوم هو أول لقاء لنا.
You beat him up before, didn't you?
لقد ضربته من قبل ، أليس كذلك؟
And you did it more than once.
وقمت بذلك أكثر من مرة.
I did beat him up once.
لقد ضربته مرة واحدة.
But that was the only time.
لكن هذه كانت المرة الوحيدة.
Do you know He Jiashu?
هل تعرف هو جياشو؟
He Jiashu?
انه جياشو؟
I don't.
أنا لا.
But he knows you.
لكنه يعرفك.
(You heard from Chen Yu)
(سمعت من تشين يو)
(that we were going to deploy our men, right?)
(أننا سننشر رجالنا ، أليس كذلك؟)
(Who else did you tell)
(من غيرك أخبرته)
(after receiving the news?)
(بعد تلقي الخبر؟)
How did you enter the drug rehab center
كيف دخلت إلى مركز إعادة التأهيل من المخدرات
and how did you get out?
وكيف خرجت؟
You have someone who can protect you in the Public Security Bureau?
هل لديك شخص يمكنه حمايتك في مكتب الأمن العام؟
Or is he in Mengka?
أم هو في مينكا؟
Who is that person?
من يكون ذلك الشخص؟
Do I know him?
هل أعرفه؟
Officer!
ضابط!
What kind of questions are these?
ما نوع هذه الأسئلة؟
Why are you asking me
لماذا انت تسالني
about these sidekicks?
حول هذه الصديقات؟
Don't you know
لا تعرف
what happened last night?
ماذا حدث الليلة الماضية
Can't you just ask me about what happened last night?
ألا يمكنك أن تسألني فقط عما حدث الليلة الماضية؟
Why did you even bring me here?
لماذا حتى أحضرتني إلى هنا؟
Who told you to burn down the tea factory?
من قال لك أن تحرق مصنع الشاي؟
Burn down the tea factory?
حرق مصنع الشاي؟
You guys think I torched the tea factory?
هل تعتقدون يا رفاق أنني أشعلت النيران في مصنع الشاي؟
How could it be me?
كيف يمكن أن يكون أنا؟
You work for K, don't you?
أنت تعمل لدى K ، أليس كذلك؟
Who's your boss?
من هو رئيسك في العمل؟
My boss?
مديري؟
My boss is Liu Kaihua.
رئيسي هو Liu Kaihua.
Do you know him?
هل تعرفه؟
Liu Kaihua
ليو كيهوا
is my uncle.
هو عمي.
He was the one who told me
كان هو الذي قال لي
to do all of these tonight.
للقيام بكل هذه الليلة.
What's with the questions?
ما بالأسئلة؟
Do you guys think I'm a criminal?
هل تعتقدون يا رفاق أنني مجرم؟
Officer,
ضابط،
I risked my life
لقد خاطرت بحياتي
to film the videos
لتصوير مقاطع الفيديو
that you guys are watching
التي تشاهدونها يا رفاق
on your computer screen right now,
على شاشة جهاز الكمبيوتر الخاص بك الآن ،
did you know that?
هل كنت تعلم هذا؟
Why are you shouting?
لماذا تصرخ؟
Everyone present
الجميع حاضر
will have to be interrogated.
سيتعين استجوابه.
No exceptions are allowed.
لا استثناءات مسموح بها.
Understood?
فهمت؟
I don't!
أنا لا!
I filmed the videos for you guys.
لقد صورت الفيديوهات لكم يا رفاق.
If you have any other questions,
إذا كان لديك أي أسئلة أخرى ،
you can ask your chief of detachment.
يمكنك أن تسأل رئيس مفرزة الخاص بك.
K made the deal with you, right?
K عقد الصفقة معك ، أليس كذلك؟
Since they've agreed to make a deal with you,
بما أنهم وافقوا على عقد صفقة معك ،
I assume you've met many of their members.
أفترض أنك قابلت العديد من أعضائها.
Who are they?
من هؤلاء؟
The deal that couldn't be done three years ago,
الصفقة التي لم يكن من الممكن إتمامها قبل ثلاث سنوات ،
I'll do it today.
سأفعل ذلك اليوم.
On account of our first encounter,
بسبب لقاءنا الأول ،
I'll leave you with a complete body.
سأتركك بجسد كامل.
Sit.
يجلس.
Even if you know the truth,
حتى لو كنت تعرف الحقيقة ،
your dad cannot be revived.
لا يمكن إحياء والدك.
You won't get off this easily
لن تحصل على هذا بسهولة
if I see you
اذا انا اراك
in Yunhe again.
في Yunhe مرة أخرى.
They torched the tea factory.
أحرقوا مصنع الشاي.
They wanted to take your life.
أرادوا أن يأخذوا حياتك.
Even so, you're still trying to defend them?
مع ذلك ، ما زلت تحاول الدفاع عنهم؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Who are the members of K?
من هم أعضاء K؟
Who's the boss of K?
من هو رئيس K؟
(Uncle,)
(اخو الام،)
(are you coming home for dinner?)
(هل ستعود إلى المنزل لتناول العشاء؟)
Buy a steam pot chicken
قم بشراء وعاء دجاج على البخار
on your way home.
في طريقك للبيت.
Wu Zhenfeng, answer me!
وو Zhenfeng ، أجبني!
It was Jiang Lei.
كان جيانغ لي.
Go and ask Jiang Lei.
اذهب واسأل جيانغ لي.
He knows
هو يعرف
much more than me.
أكثر مني.
Are you doing this on purpose?
هل تفعل هذا عن قصد؟
[First People's Hospital of Yunhe County] [Outpatient Department]
[مستشفى الشعب الأول في مقاطعة يونخه] [قسم العيادات الخارجية]
Dad.
أب.
I have no appetite.
ليس لدي أي شهية.
Just leave it there for now.
فقط اتركه هناك الآن.
I'll have it later.
سآخذها لاحقًا.
Dad, I'm sorry.
أبي ، أنا آسف.
I shouldn't have trusted Wu Zhenfeng.
لا ينبغي أن أثق في Wu Zhenfeng.
You were implicated because of me.
لقد تورطت بسببي.
Silly girl,
فتاة سخيفة،
I'm your dad.
أنا والدك.
I will never be implicated by you
لن أتورط أبدا من قبلك
Dad,
أب،
I believe Chen Yu and the rest
أعتقد تشين يو والباقي
will definitely get to the bottom of it.
سيصل بالتأكيد إلى الجزء السفلي منه.
I do not
انا لست
expect much from him.
نتوقع منه الكثير.
Yang.
أيّ.
Look at what we brought.
انظر إلى ما قدمناه.
Uncle Lin, pass it to me.
العم لين ، مررها لي.
Mr. Yang.
السيد.  أيّ.
How was it?
كيف وجدته؟
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Mr. Yang, are you okay?
السيد يانغ ، هل أنت بخير؟
Mr. Zhuo,
السيد جو ،
I assume you knew their plan
أفترض أنك تعرف خطتهم
from the start?
من البداية؟
Boss,
رئيس،
Dong's goods have arrived.
وصلت بضائع دونغ.
Hao Dong, what do you mean by this?
هاو دونغ ، ماذا تقصد بهذا؟
♪The wind♪
الريح ♪
♪Continues to blow tirelessly♪
♪ يواصل النفخ بلا كلل ♪
♪Above the sky♪
فوق السماء ♪
♪Exists an empty space♪
توجد مساحة فارغة
♪Taking a path♪
اتخاذ مسار ♪
♪Adhering to my original aspiration♪
التمسك بطموحي الأصلي ♪
♪Wounds and pain♪
الجروح والألم ♪
♪Are medals honoring my bravery♪
هي ميداليات تكريم لشجاعي
♪This story♪
♪ هذه القصة ♪
♪It may not be eulogized♪
لا يجوز تأبينه ♪
♪But I remain passionate♪
♪ لكنني ما زلت شغوفًا ♪
♪And willing to give you my all♪
♪ وعلى استعداد لأعطيك كل ما لدي
♪There are always some people♪
♪ هناك دائما بعض الناس
♪Bearing the burden during the peaceful years♪
تحمل العبء في سنوات السلم ♪
♪When breaking out♪
عند الخروج ♪
♪The blazing fire and the raging flame♪
النيران المشتعلة واللهب الهائج
♪Who can see clearly♪
من يستطيع أن يرى بوضوح
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪ ماذا علي أن أتحمل؟ ♪
♪The only way out♪
السبيل الوحيد للخروج ♪
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
هو حرق جسري ♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪ صرخت أسناني ♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪ وحاول أن أحميك بأفضل ما أستطيع
♪Deep down♪
في العمق ♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
الماضي مستمر ولم يتغير أحد أبدًا
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
مهما كانت صعوبة
♪Fly over♪
♪ حلق فوق ♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
السماء والأرض ♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪ الى نهاية العالم ♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
من ذكريات محفورة على قلبي ♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪ سأولد من جديد ♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪ لن أنظر إلى الوراء أبدًا
♪And never ask what if♪
♪ ولا تسأل أبدًا ماذا لو ♪
♪Who can see clearly♪
من يستطيع أن يرى بوضوح
♪What I have to bear?♪
♪ ماذا علي أن أتحمل؟ ♪
♪The only way out♪
السبيل الوحيد للخروج ♪
♪Is to burn my bridges♪
هو حرق جسري ♪
♪I grit my teeth♪
♪ صرخت أسناني ♪
♪And try to protect you the best I can♪
♪ وحاول أن أحميك بأفضل ما أستطيع
♪Deep down♪
في العمق ♪
♪The past continues and no one has ever changed♪
الماضي مستمر ولم يتغير أحد أبدًا
♪No matter how difficult it is♪
مهما كانت صعوبة
♪Fly over♪
♪ حلق فوق ♪
♪Heaven and Earth♪
السماء والأرض ♪
♪To the end of the world♪
♪ الى نهاية العالم ♪
♪From memories engraved upon my heart♪
من ذكريات محفورة على قلبي ♪
♪I shall be reborn♪
♪ سأولد من جديد ♪
♪I'll never look back♪
♪ لن أنظر إلى الوراء أبدًا
♪And never ask what if♪
♪ ولا تسأل أبدًا ماذا لو ♪